{
    "subject": "Mai_Zetterling",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Doctor_Glas__film_",
    "human_readable": "Mai Zetterling directed the film Doctor Glas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8655206561088562,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Mai Zetterling."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8602311611175537,
            "question": "Who directed the film Doctor Glas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8436187505722046,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Mai Zetterling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.675667941570282,
            "question": "What makes Mai Zetterling a notable director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5399153828620911,
            "question": "What kind of work did Mai Zetterling do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4234599471092224,
            "question": "What genre might the film Doctor Glas belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40373823046684265,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Doctor Glas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3996116518974304,
            "question": "Is Doctor Glas a fictional or non-fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25444653630256653,
            "question": "Were there any critical reviews or awards associated with Doctor Glas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.061645638197660446,
            "question": "Who are some other famous directors who have made films about similar themes?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mai Zetterling directed the film Doctor Glas.",
            "html": "yago_887_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any critical reviews or awards associated with Doctor Glas?",
            "html": "yago_887_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Doctor Glas a fictional or non-fictional film?",
            "html": "yago_887_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Doctor Glas?",
            "html": "yago_887_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_887_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_887/re-ranker-msmarco/68.txt, Mai Zetterling directed the film \"Doctor Glas\", which is adapted from the novel of the same name by Hjalmar S\u00f6derberg."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context provided mentions that Mai Zetterling directed the film \"Dr. Glas,\" which is also referred to as \"Doctor Glas\" in other documents. Therefore, the statement \"Mai Zetterling directed the film Doctor Glas\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}